<?xml version="1.0"?>
<configuration>
	<placeholders>
		<placeholder id="template_name">Workday to ServiceNow Worker Migration</placeholder>
	</placeholders>
	<sections>
		<section id="use_case">
As a Workday admin I want to migrate workers from Workday to users in ServiceNow.

This Anypoint Template should serve as a foundation for the process of migrating Workers from Workday instance to Users in ServiceNow, being able to specify filtering criteria and desired behavior if a user already exists in the destination system. 

As implemented, this Anypoint Template leverages the [Batch Module](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/Batch+Processing).
The batch job is divided into Input, Process and On Complete stages.
During the Input stage the Anypoint Template will query Workday for all the existing active workers that match the filter criteria. The criteria is based on manipulations starting from the given date.
The last step of the Process stage will create or update the users in ServiceNow based on if a user already exists in the system.
Finally during the On Complete stage the Anypoint Template will both output statistics data into the console and send a notification e-mail with the results of the batch execution. 
		</section>
		<section id="considerations">
<![CDATA[
There are a couple of things you should take into account before running this Anypoint Template:

1. **Workday e-mail uniqueness**: The e-mail can be repeated for two or more accounts (or missing). Therefore Workday accounts with duplicate emails will be removed from processing in the Input stage.
2. Users in ServiceNow are matched with Workday Workers based on the `user_name`. If user_name is not specified then the matching is based on the `email`, `first_name` and `last_name`.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="run_it">
<![CDATA[

In any of the ways you would like to run this Anypoint Template this is an example of the output you'll see after hitting the HTTP connector:

<pre>
<h1>Batch Process initiated</h1>
<b>ID:</b>6eea3cc6-7c96-11e3-9a65-55f9f3ae584e<br/>
<b>Records to Be Processed: </b>9<br/>
<b>Start execution on: </b>Tue Oct 13 18:05:33 GMT-03:00 2015
</pre>
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_cloudhub">
<![CDATA[
Once your app is all set up and started, supposing you choose `wdayworkermigration` as domain name to trigger the use case, you just need to hit `http://wdayworkermigration.cloudhub.io/migrateworkers` and report will be sent to the e-mail configured.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="running_on_standalone">
<![CDATA[
After this, to trigger the use case you just need to hit the local HTTP connector with the port you configured in your file. If this is, for instance, `9090` then you should hit: `http://localhost:9090/migrateworkers` and this will output a summary report and send it in the e-mail.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="application_configuration">
		<![CDATA[
+ http.port `9090`
+ migration.startDate `"2015-09-11T00:00:00.000Z"`

#### Workday Connector configuration
+ wday.user `joan`
+ wday.tenant `acme_pt1`
+ wday.password `joanPass123`
+ wdayf.hostname `your_impl-cc.workday.com`

#### ServiceNow Connector 
+ snow.user `snow_user1`
+ snow.password `ExamplePassword881`
+ snow.endpoint `https://instance.service-now.com`

#### SMTP Services configuration
+ smtp.host `smtp.gmail.com`
+ smtp.port `587`
+ smtp.user `sender%40gmail.com`
+ smtp.password `secret`

#### Mail details
+ mail.from `users.report%40mulesoft.com`
+ mail.to `user@mulesoft.com`
+ mail.subject `Users Migration Report`
]]>
		</section>	
		<section id="api_calls">
			<![CDATA[There are no special considerations regarding API calls.  ]]>
		</section>	
		<section id="default_endpoints_xml">
		<![CDATA[
This is the file where you will find the inbound and outbound sides of your integration app.
This Template has only an [HTTP Listener Connector](http://www.mulesoft.org/documentation/display/current/HTTP+Listener+Connector) as the way to trigger the use case.

**HTTP Listener Connector** - Start Report Generation

+ `${http.port}` is set as a property to be defined either on a property file or in CloudHub environment variables.
+ The path configured by default is `migrateworkers` and you are free to change for the one you prefer.
+ The host name for all endpoints in your CloudHub configuration should be defined as `localhost`. CloudHub will then route requests from your application domain URL to the endpoint.
+ The endpoint is a *request-response* since as a result of calling it the response will be the total of Workers synced and filtered by the criteria specified.
]]>
		</section>
		<section id="default_business_logic_xml">
		<![CDATA[
Functional aspect of the Anypoint Template is implemented on this XML, directed by one flow responsible of excecuting the logic.
For the pourpose of this particular Anypoint Template the *mainFlow* just executes the Batch Job which handles all the logic of it.
This flow has Exception Strategy that basically consists on invoking the *defaultChoiseExceptionStrategy* defined in *errorHandling.xml* file.
]]>
		</section>
	</sections>
</configuration>